Natalia Marchenko

Junior OA Manual

SUMMARY

Since September 2023, I have been studying the theory of testing, as well as the basic techniques of working with various tester tools. I have no commercial experience but would like to have the opportunity to further develop my skills in quality assurance

SKILLS

Jira

Test Documentation

SDLC process

Test levels

SCRUM

Testcaselab

SQL

HTML

Bug reports

Static testing

Postman

API

SOAP

Test Design technics

CSS

Mobile Testing

EDUCATION

Publishing and editing at Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

1997-2003

ADDITIONAL COURSES AND TRAININGS

 QA Manual at Hillel IT School **EXCELLENT**

2023

- Fundamentals of software testing at QATestlab

https://clients.qatestlab.com/achievements/nfydh4323zvc2gcff7b2f0uz

2023

- Fundamentals of software testing at Prometeus
- 2023 https://certs.prometheus.org.ua/downloads/c1ae332d5a124c5cbe07f4fe8f4a9233/Certificate.pdf
- Fundamentals of software testing at Дія.Освіта https://osvita.diia.gov.ua/share/Ou-wWrKFtNvCrOZ1TtTlvcuTpedNRJ3I

2023

• English Pre-Intermediate at Hillel IT School

2023

WORK EXPERIENCE

editor at publishing house "Autocenter" editing texts for language, grammar, and style, communicating with authors, adhering to editorial standards, developing text structure, ensuring proper formatting, collaborating with other departments, and maintaining the quality of publications.

advertising manager at publishing house "Blitz Inform"

2003-2004

1998-2003

market analysis, strategic planning, creating advertising materials, selecting advertising platforms, client communication, analytics and performance measurement, establishing partnerships, budget management. market analysis, strategic planning, creating advertising materials, selecting advertising platforms, client communication, analytics and performance measurement, establishing partnerships, budget management



CONTACTS

Location

Kyiv, Ukraine

! Remote only

vmsoft.ua@gmail.com

+380633666703

Telegram

https://t.me/natalym01

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nataliamarchenko-5a4173293/

LANGUAGES

English B1

event manager at Gestalt Consulting Group
 planning and organizing events, budgeting, client communication, selecting and
 coordinating vendors, venue selection and decoration, marketing and
 advertising, program coordination, logistics and safety management, and event

manager at online store of women's clothing
managing product inventory, optimizing website design, enhancing online
sales strategies, providing customer service, overseeing marketing and
advertising efforts, handling order processing and shipping, analyzing
market trends, negotiating with suppliers, and tracking store performance.

qa manual at online store of women's clothing
testing functionality, user interaction, payment and delivery processes,
cross-device compatibility, database integrity, security, browser compatibility,

trainee at QATestLab
 Quality Assurance Tester

updates and new features

analysis and reporting.

2023

qroup pet-project at Team Challenge

2023 - present

2016 - present

I am currently participating in a group pet-project, where I assume the role of a Quality Assurance specialist. We are working on an online shop and chat application. My responsibilities include reviewing documentation and layouts, creating checklists, conducting checks, writing bug reports, and compiling checklists for backend testing using Swagger. Additionally, I am responsible for documenting and reporting bugs found in the backend.

новву

travel and learning foreign languages